Herman, Francine Collection on Hospitality Workers and Collective Bargaining 6273
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Francine Herman Collection on Hospitality Workers and Collective Bargaining
1938-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Herman, Francine
6273
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
6349521
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 09, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4270: Francine Herman collection of Alice H. Cook Memorial Celebration files
Collective bargaining -- Hospitality industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Herman, Francine; Hotel Association of New York City
6349521
- Hotel Association of New York City: By-Laws., 1938-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Hotel Association of New York City. Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Collective Bargaining Agreement., 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Memoranda., 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Memoranda., 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Memoranda., 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Memoranda., 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Hotel Association of New York City: Grievances., 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hospitality and Food Service Workers. Eight City Benefits Comparison. (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Gill, Richard E. Hospitality Management Co-Op: Doing It Right, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Starke, Ralph to Nick Coussis., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence.